[
 {"0":{"Question":"How many degrees around a point?", "answer": "360"}},
 {"1":{"Question":"How many centimetres in a metre?", "answer": "100"}},
 {"2":{"Question":"How many degrees in a quadrilateral?", "answer": "360"}},
 {"3": {"Question":"How many sides does a triangle have?", "answer": "3"}},
 {"4": {"Question":"What is an approximation to pi to 3 dp?", "answer": "3.142"}},
 {"5": {"Question":"How many minutes between 9.30pm and 10.18pm?", "answer": "48"}},
 {"6": {"Question":"How far do I travel at 40mph in 3 hours?", "answer": "120"}},
 {"7": {"Question":"What is 2x + 5x - 4x?", "answer": "3x"}},
 {"8": {"Question":"What is the result of 5+4x9?", "answer": "41"}},
 {"9": {"Question":"If 60 is divided in the ratio 2:3 what is the smaller share?", "answer": "24"}},
 {"10": {"Question":"How many degrees around a point?", "answer": "360"}},
 {"11": {"Question":"How many metres in a kilometre?", "answer": "1000"}},
 {"12": {"Question":"What is 50% as a decimal?", "answer": "0.5"}},
 {"13": {"Question":"How many sides does a hexagon have?", "answer": "6"}},
 {"14": {"Question":"What is my speed if I travel 50 km in 2 hours?", "answer": "25"}},
 {"15": {"Question":"What is the third prime number?", "answer": "5"}},
 {"16": {"Question": "What is the HCF of 12 and 20?", "answer": "4"}},
 {"17": {"Question":"What is -5y-2y + 9y?", "answer": "2y"}},
 {"18": {"Question":"What is the result of (12+3) x (6 divided by 2)?", "answer": "45"}},
 {"19": {"Question":"What is the density of an object if its mass is 10kg and its volume is 5 cubic metres?", "answer": "2"}}
]